karmasnack.com 2013-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Karma Snack | Web Agency | KarmaSnack

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Karma Snack LLC.  
Because Karma Snack LLC wants to demonstrate its firm commitment to your  
privacy, Karma Snack LLC has agreed to disclose its information gathering  
and dissemination practices. Karma Snack LLC will notify you of: 

  * What information is collected from you through the web site
  * The organization collecting the information
  * How the information is used
  * With whom the information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and  
distribution of the information
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss,  
misuse or alteration of information under Karma Snack LLC control
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

If you feel that Karma Snack LLC is not abiding by its  
posted privacy policy, you wish to modify information previously given, or have  
any questions regarding the privacy policy, please contact us.

  * **MINORS**

Karma Snack LLC does not knowingly collect personally  
identifiable information from children under 13 years of age.

  * **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

Karma Snack LLC is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.  
We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different  
from what is disclosed in this statement. Karma Snack LLC collects  
information through this site from our prospective and existing clients at  
several different points on our web site. We use their contact information to  
send information about our company and to service. Users may opt-out of  
receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Contact and  
Financial information that is collected is used for verifying your name,  
address and other information, as well as to bill you for your use of our  
services using information from third party sources. Information about your  
computer hardware and software is automatically collected by Karma Snack LLC  
and may be shared in aggregate with third parties. This information includes:  
your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website  
addresses. This information is not tied to personally identifiable information.  
This information is used by Karma Snack LLC to maintain and improve the  
quality of the service and to generate statistics regarding use of the Karma Snack LLC site.

We use third party services to bill for services and to provide other services.  
We store the transcripts from these services for customer service improvement.  
These third party service providers are not permitted to use your information  
for any secondary purposes. 

  * **CHOICE/OPT-OUT**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of  
receiving communications from us and our partners.

This site gives users the following options for removing  
their information from our database to not receive future communications or to  
no longer receive our service.

    * You can send e-mail.

Please note that participation in certain activities on our  
web site may be limited if personally identifiable information is not submitted  
for the user.

  * **COOKIES**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive  
containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to  
any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes  
their browser, a cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie  
for Karma Snack LLC, the user would not have to log in a password more than  
once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they  
may still use our site however without cookies the user may not have access to  
certain features on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target  
the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for  
example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these  
cookies.

  * **LINKS**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware  
that Karma Snack LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of such  
other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to  
read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally  
identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information  
collected by Karma Snack LLC.

  * **SECURITY**

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to  
help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or  
disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on  
computer systems with limited access, that are located in controlled  
facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit  
card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption,  
such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

  * **DISCLOSURE**

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and  
other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not  
otherwise described in this Privacy Agreement. By way of example (without  
limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the  
government or third parties under certain circumstances as required by law,  
third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private  
communications.

  * **ACCOUNT ESTABLISHMENT**

Upon sign up for our membership, Karma Snack LLC will send  
an e-mail to the e-mail address provided during registration. This is to  
establish that the new account is a valid account and your password will be  
delivered to you at this time. Accounts with invalid e-mail addresses will  
not be able to participate in all features of Karma Snack LLC.

  * **SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES**

We will send the user site and service announcement updates.  
Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain  
important information about the service. We communicate with the user to  
provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to the account via  
e-mail or telephone.

  * **NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those  
changes on this page so all users are always aware of what information we  
collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  
If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a  
manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we  
will prominently post a notice on the page for 30 days. We may also make a  
reasonable effort to notify users by way of an e-mail. Users have a choice as  
to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will  
use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the  
information was collected.

This Privacy policy was last updated on June 5, 2012.

Last Updated 08/23/13
